乔伊  你慢一点
Joey, would you slow down?
报纸不会在半夜一点就全部卖光的
They're not gonna be sold out of papers at one o'clock in the morning.
我好兴奋  第一次有我的剧评
I'm excited! I've never been reviewed before!
你演国王演得太精采了  可圈可点  真的
You were so amazing as the king. I was really impressed, I was.
不过你知道吗
But you know what?
你下次可以考虑穿上内裤
You might wanna consider wearing underwear next time.
因为你登上宝座时  观众可以看到你的...
When you sat on the throne, you could just kind of see your...
龙根
... royal subjects.
有了  在这里
Here it is! Here it is!
"唯一比盲目而幼稚的导演更蹩脚的"
"The only thing worse than the mindless adolescent direction...
"就是乔瑟夫·崔比安尼诠释国王形象的拙劣演技"
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingly unskilled portrayal of the king."
那只是一个人的意见
Okay, look. That is one guy's opinion.
别放心上  菲比  念你的
All right? Pheebs, read yours.
"唯一比盲目而幼稚的导演更蹩脚的"
"The only thing worse than the mindless, adolescent direction"
还有没有其它报纸
Anybody have a different paper?
罗斯  念你的
Ross, read yours.
我不想念
I don't want to.
乔伊  亲爱的  他们自己都不知所云
Joey, honey, they don't know what they're talking about.
那不一定
Maybe they do.
我演了十年  还没混出个名堂
I've been doin' this ten years and I haven't gotten anywhere.
也不是没有原因的
There's gotta be a reason.
别这样  你现在是耕耘阶段
Come on, you're just paying your dues.
不  太难了
No, no, no. It's too hard.
这不值得  我不干了
It's not worth it. I quit.
别这样
Come on, Joey!
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait one minute. Wait a minute.
包你听了会有改观
I believe this will change your mind.
"在这出平凡的戏里"
"ln a mediocre play,
"乔瑟夫·崔比安尼一举跃上绝妙新水准..."
Joseph Tribbiani was able to achieve brilliant levels of...
接153页
Continued on page 153.
超级烂
sucking."
小时候  我的志愿是当兽医
When I was little,I used to want to be a veteranarian.
然后我发现得把手伸到牛的体内
But then I found out you have to put your hands into cows and stuff..
你好吗
Are you okay?
很好  只是水深火热的一天
Just a tough day at work, you know?
剑龙倒了  一个小孩出不来了
Stegosaurus fell over, trapped a kid.
我认得这件夹克  这是风趣鲍比的夹克
I know this jacket. This is Fun Bobby's jacket!
他在哪里  他在这里  对不对
Where is he? He's here, isn't he?
-或许  -别耍我
- Maybe. - Don't toy with me.
盖勒
Geller!
风趣鲍比
Hey, Fun Bobby!
你一直在锻炼吧
Hey! You been working out?
才没有
Not at all.
我爱这家伙
I love this guy!
好高兴听说你跟我妹妹复合了
I'm so psyched to hear you're back with myn sister.
-我们都很高兴  -我错过了什么吗
- You and me both! - Hey, so what'd I miss, what'd I miss, c'mon?
我们在努力安慰乔伊
We were just trying to make Joey feel better.
需要我把你举起来吗
Hey, do you need me to pick you up?
不  我没事了  真的
No, I'm alright man. Really.
不  我要把你举起来
No, I'm picking you up!
不  真的  我不需要你把我...
Hey no, seriously, I don't need you to pick me...
好吧  还是有用
Alright! It still works.
在我走之前  有谁还要我举起来
OK, now before I go, does anybody else need to be picked up?
我还是走好了
I'm still gonna go.
回头见  宝贝
OK, I'll see you later babe.
我们要公开亲热  你们还是别看了
Public display of affection coming up. You can avert your eyes.
-再见  -再见
- See you. - Bye.
风趣鲍比真不错
Fun Bobby is so great.
可不是吗
Oh, isn't he?
我觉得这一回我们可能走下去  他让我感觉特别好
I think this time it may work with him. I mean, he just makes me feel so good
这几个月我都很颓废  没工作  没男友
and I've been feeling so lousy this last couple of months, no job, no boyfriend.
至少现在我有一样了
Well, at least my cup is half full.
有一样"爱"
Half full of love!
为庆祝我们交往两周  他周末带我去他表哥的小屋
For our two-week anniversary, he's taking me to his cousin's cabin for the weekend.
"爱"的小屋
Cabin of love!
我们今晚喝了好多酒
We went through a lot of wine tonight, you guys.
真的吗  我才喝了两杯
Really? I only had two glasses.
我只喝了一杯
I had a glass.
我两杯
Two.
我喝了一杯
I had one glass.
我用这个可爱的印有...
I had about a mugful in this lovely
"我在自然历史博物馆看到骨头了"的杯子喝了一大杯
I-got-boned-at-the- Museum-of-Natural-History mug.
这么说的话  顶多两瓶
Okay, so that's what? Two bottles.
可这里有五个空瓶
And yet somehow we went through five?
那又怎么样  他今晚喝多了
So what? So he drank a lot tonight.
没错  不过现在回想起来
Yeah but, you know, now that I think about it,
我觉得风趣鲍比酒不离手
I don't think I've ever seen Fun Bobby without a... a drink in his hand.
你们有没有注意过  他故事开头总是
Yeah, you know, did you notice how he always starts his stories with,
"我喝得烂醉了"  或是"我们快喝趴下了"
... "Okay, I was so wasted!" or "Oh, we were so bombed!"
"我醒来后发现我在康州一辆清道车里面"
"So I wake up and I'm in this dumpster in Connecticut!"
摩妮卡  你们在一起时  他哪次没喝酒的
Monica, have you ever been with him when he wasn't drinking?
只是恰巧而已  我们去的地方都会喝酒的
We just happen to go to a lot of places where you might drink.
我们去品酒会  怎么可能不来杯酒
How do you go to a wine-tasting without having a drink?
要不就是去俱乐部  或是...
Or to a club, or to the...
动物园
...zoo.
谢了  瑞秋  里面有没有脱脂奶
Thanks. Rach, does this have nonfat milk?
不知道  你尝尝看吧
I don't know, want you to taste it.
-没  - 来不及了  抱歉  你喝过了
- No. - Too late, sorry, you already had some.
我们把这些都调成爱尔兰咖啡怎么样
What do you say we make these coffees Irish?
蛋糕
Cake!
对  我去拿蛋糕
Yeah, we're gonna get some cake.
你最近好像把很多东西都做成爱尔兰式的
It seems like you've been making an awful lot of stuff "lrish" lately.
我很想弄成比利时式的  可饼干很难塞进酒瓶子里
I'd make them Belgian, but the waffles are hard to get into that flask.
-鲍比  -好吧
- Bobby.  - Yeah, okay.
听着  这或许不关我的事  或许有关  我不知道
Look, maybe this is none of my business, or maybe it is, I don't know...
我有点担心你
but, uh, I'm kind of worried about you.
这不是第一次有人跟我说这事了
OK, look, this isn't the first time somebody's said something to me about this,
我老是为我自己找一些借口
but, I don't know... I always made excuses about it, like...
像是"我是为了应酬"
'I'm just a social drinker,'
或"喝吧  今天是国旗日"
Or "Come on, it's Flag Day!"
那你现在用什么借口呢
So, what are you saying now?
我要说
I guess I'm saying...
我戒戒看
... I'll try and quit.
我喜欢你担心我的样子
I like that you worry about me.
怎么了
So, what's going on?
我要试着戒酒了
I am gonna try and quit drinking.
为什么
Oh! Why?
猜谁又回演艺圈了
Guess who's back in show bussiness!
洛恩·格林
Lorne Greene?
不是  菲比  知道为什么吗  他死了
No, no, Phoebs. You know why? Cause he's dead.
不是吧
Oh, no.
我想这似乎有点苦乐参半
OK, I guess this is gonna seem kinda bittersweet now,
是乔伊  正是他
... but Joey, that's who!
我经纪人叫我去《我们的日子》试镜
My agent called me with an audition for Days Of Our Lives!
真牛
Kick ass!
一定要庆祝  该开个肥皂剧主题派对
We have to celebrate! We should do a soap opera theme.
对  我们可以一起上床  然后其中一个人失忆
Hey, yeah... we could all sleep together and then one of us could get amnesia.
瑞秋  你什么时候下班  晚上大家聚一聚
Hey Rach, what time do you get off? We're all gonna do something tonight.
其实我已经下班了  但我另有安排
Well, actually, I'm already done. But I kind of got plans.
你有别的朋友
You have other friends?
对  我有约会
Yeah... I, uhh... I have a... I have a date.
什么
What?
跟男人
With a man?
怎么  我有约会有什么奇怪的
What? What is so strange about me having a date?
那罗斯怎么办
What about Ross?
你还在为列清单的事跟他生气吗
I mean, are you still mad at him cause he made that list about you?
没  我不生气了
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
我对他一点也"没什么"了
I'm not really "anything" at him anymore.
-你在说什么呢  -我不知道
- What are you talking about? - I don't know.
不管我之前是什么感觉  我...
Whatever I was feeling, I'm...
现在没了
... not.
你们就差一点点
But you guys came so close.
我知道  对不起  各位
Oh, I know, I'm sorry you guys.
你们只好习惯我不会跟罗斯约会这个事实
You're just gonna have to get used to the fact that I will not be dating Ross.
他来了
Here he is.
各位  这是洛斯
Guys, this is Russ.
不  我不是说你没才华  你非常有才华
No. I'm not saying you're not talented, you're very talented.
那只鸟死了之后  剩下的戏份就不多了
It's just with the bird dead and all, there's very little act left.
亲爱的  放我一马  好吗
Honey, give me a break, will you?
我等会儿再打给你
I'll talk to you later.
我最喜爱的客户来了
There's my favorite client!
告诉我  亲爱的  试镜结果如何
So tell me, darling, how was the audition?
我觉得挺顺利  他们要我周四复试
I think it went well. I got a callback for Thursday.
乔伊  你见过我欣喜若狂吗
Joey! Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
没
No.
看我
Well, here it is.
好  对了  有件事我想跟你谈谈
Okay! Listen, there's something I want to talk to you about.
电视台的选角小姐
The network casting lady...
罗莉是不是很棒
Oh, isn't Lori a doll?
对  她很棒
Yeah. She's great.
可我觉得她好像对我有点意思
But I kind of got the feeling that she was sort of coming on to me.
我觉得如果我想得到那个角色的话  就要...
And I definitely would get the part if I were to, you know....
派我的"小将军"出马
if I would have sent the Little General in.
我懂了  我现在就打个电话
I see! Well, I'm just gonna put in a call here...
摸清门道  然后想想办法
...and we'll find out what's going on and straighten it out.
你好  请转罗莉
Hi. Lori, please.
亲爱的
Hi, darling!
乔伊·崔比安尼适合出租车司机那个角色吗
So how 'bout Joey Tribbiani for the part of the cab driver?
他是不是很出色
Isn't he terrific?
好  美女  回头再聊
Okay, doll, talk to you later.
对  你必须跟她上床
Yeah, you're gonna have to sleep with her.
-你怎么了  -是风趣鲍比
- What's the matter? - Fun Bobby.
怎么  他又喝酒了吗
What? Isn't he sober?
他是没喝酒
Oh, he's sober all right.
只是我发现  风趣鲍比风趣是有原因的
Just turns out that Fun Bobby was fun for a reason.
拿去吧  甜心
All right, here you go, sweetie.
谢了  要不要听一个有趣的故事
Thanks. You wanna hear something funny?
当然要
Oh, God, yes!
只要一过了午夜  这附近的五金店就全都关门了
There are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
真好笑
That is funny.
前几天晚上我要买把榔头  就出门在附近逛了逛
I needed to buy a hammer the other night and I'm out walking around the neighborhood.
但显然
But apparently...
过了午夜  村里就没有五金店营业了
...there are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
甜心  你不是该去面试了吗
Ahhh, hey honey? Don't you have to be at your interview now?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
各位再见了
See you guys.
再见
Bye...
无聊至极的鲍比
...ridiculously dull Bobby.
老天
Oh, my God.
他还没那么糟
He's not that bad.
没那么糟  你没听到那个故事吗
Not that bad? Did you not hear the hammer story?
好吧  别那么挑剔
Okay, don't get all squinky.
也许你该身历其境  才会觉得好笑
Maybe it was just the kind of story where you have to be there.
但我下半辈子
But I'm gonna be there!
都会身历其境
For the rest of my life.
我不能跟他分手  是我让他戒酒的
I can't break up with him. I'm the one who made him quit drinking.
他无聊是因为我
He is dull because me!
好了  别这么说
OK. Don't say that.
也许他一直很无聊  你只是...
He's probably always been dull. You just, you know...
让他本性流露
...set it free.
罗斯
Hey, Ross.
洛斯
Hi, Russ.
我再收拾两张桌子  我们就可以走了  好吗
I've got two more tables to clean, and then we'll go.
好  我就坐这儿好了
OK. I'll just sit here and...
跟你的
...chat with your...
"朋友"一起聊天
...friend-type people.
瑞秋
Rachel?
你知道你在干什么吗
So, you know what you're doing, right?
当服务员
Waitressing?
是  又不是
Well, yeah. But, no. I mean....
洛斯不会让你想起某个人吗
Doesn't Russ just remind you of someone?
鲍勃·萨吉特
Bob Saget?
还真是
Oh, yeah!
不对
No, no, no!
天啊
Oh, my, oh!
怎么了
What's wrong?
我...
I...
她心情不好是因为...
She's upset because...
她不小心把一只蜘蛛涂在吐司上了
...she buttered a spider into her toast this morning.
好吧
All right.
听我说  菲比  别往心里去
Listen, Pheebs. This is gonna be okay.
罗斯  洛斯  洛斯  罗斯
Ross, Russ. Russ, Ross.
你是瑞秋的朋友吗
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
是  我是
Yes. Yes, I am.
你是瑞秋的朋友吗
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
事实上  我是...
Actually, I'm kind of a...
可以说是...
...you know...
瑞秋的约会...
...a date-type thing...
对象
...of Rachel's.
约会
A date?
对  约会对象
Yeah. I'm her date.
你是...  你是...
Oh! Oh, you're a....
你是她的约会对象
Oh, you're the date.
其实这样也不错
This is actually good...
万一罗斯不在了  我们还有个备胎
... because if we lose Ross, we have a spare.
你是那个古生物学家
Oh! You are the paleontologist.
对  我是  那你是...
Yes. Yes, I am. And you are a....
牙周病医生
Periodontist.
瞧  他们的差别就好比黑夜和...
See? Now they're as different as night and...
深夜
...later that night.
我现在要去拿杯饮料
Well, I am going to get a beverage.
很高兴认识你
It was nice meeting you.
彼此
Ditto.
我见过洛斯了
I... Well, I met Russ.
我们什么时候各自另寻约会对象了
Hey, I didn't know we were seeing other people.
我们并没在交往  所以...
Well, we're not seeing each other, so....
我告诉你好了  我们馆里有个女的
For your information, there's a woman at the museum...
负责蛾类跟其它...
...who's curator of moths and other...
有翅生物
...winged things...
她明确表示了对我的倾慕  就像是...
...who's let it be known that she is drawn to me, much like a...
你懂的
...you know.
我到现在还跟她保持距离  但是如果你不介意
So far I've kept her at bay, but if this is the deal
对  我不介意
Well, yeah, this is the deal.
-那好  祝你晚上过得愉快  -谢谢
- Okay, well, have a nice evening. - Thank you.
-洛斯  你好了吗  -好了
- Russ, you ready? - Yeah.
她在约会
She's dating?
对  对  但你看到她在跟谁约会了吗
Yes, yes, but did you see who she was dating?
什么意思
What do you mean?
-你看不出来吗  -看出来什么
- Do you not see it? - See what?
我真搞不懂  她看中那蠢蛋哪一点
I don't know what she sees in that goober!
那个家伙讲完一句话要等上...
It takes him, what? Like, I don't know...
大概...一个礼拜
... hello, a week to get out a sentence?
是啊  烦死人了  是不是
Yeah, it's annoying, isn't it?
对
Yeah.
我猜你没被选上
I'm guessing you didn't get the part...
还是意大利来电说它饿了
...or Italy called and said it was hungry?
不  我要的话  那角色就是我的
Well, the part's mine if I want it.
老天啊
Oh, my God!
对  只要我愿意跟选角小姐上床
Yeah, if I'm willing to sleep with the casting lady.
我的
Oh, my...
老天
...God?
我等了十年才等到这个机会  钱德勒  十年
Ten years I've been waiting for a break like this. Chandlar. Ten years!
这可是《我们的日子》  实实在在能上电视的
I mean, Days of our Lives. That's actually on television!
那你要怎么做
What are you gonna do?
我可以跟她上床
I guess I could sleep with her. I mean....
我怎么能那么做呢
How can I do that?
我有一本教我一切性知识的立体书
I've got a pop-up book that told me everything I need to know.
我从没有为了角色跟人上床过
I've never slept with someone for a part.
那她...
Well, is she
抱歉
Sorry.
她长得好看吗
Is she good-looking?
好看  她长得非常好看
Yeah, she's totally good looking.
我在酒吧认识她的话  一定会请她吃早餐
I mean, if I met her in a bar, or something, I'd be buying her breakfast.
我是说跟她上床之后
You know, after having slept with her.
或许这没什么大不了的
Y'know, maybe this isn't such a big deal. Y'know,
依我看  你不但得到一份好工作  还可以跟她上床
The way that I see it is, you get a great job, and you get to have sex!
你这也算是事业美女双丰收了
Y'know, I mean, throw in a tree and a fat guy and you've got Christmas.
我只是不希望走这条捷径
I just don't think that I want it that way, though.
假如哪天我真成名了
I mean, let's say I do make it, all right?
我会怀疑当初到底是因为我的才华
I'll always look back and wonder if it was because of my talent
还是因为我的"小将军"
or because of you know, the little general.
你以前不是叫它"小少校"的吗
Didn't you use to call it "the little major"?
对  但上过丹尼斯·迪马克后  它就晋升了
Yeah, but after Denise DeMarco, I had to promote it.
两位要不要来点酒水
Can I get you something from the bar?
好  我要点杯酒
Yes, I would like something.
不  不  谢谢
No. No, thank you.
没关系  你想喝酒的话  我没问题
If you wanna drink, it's okay with me.
我要习惯这种事
I've gotta get used to it.
不  真的  我会觉得很不舒服
No, no, really. I wouldn't feel right about it.
来杯水好了
Just some water.
我冰箱里面的灯熄了
So the light went out in my refrigerator..
来杯威士忌  加冰块跟柠檬
I'd like a scotch on the rocks with a twist.
这个游戏很有趣吧  罗斯
We're having some fun now, huh, Ross?
我们再做一个好不好  洛斯
Wanna do another one? Huh, Russ?
好  十一个字母
OK. Eleven letters...
它的原子序号是101  字尾是"ium"
...atomic element number 101, ends in "ium."
镝
Dysprosium.
还镝呢
钔对不对
Try mendelevium.
二号参赛者答对了
And weenie number two has it.
除非直九的"白缎之夜"是"杜迪蓝调"唱的
Unless "Knights in White Satin" was sung by the Doody Blues.
你看不出来吗  你真看不出来吗
You don't see it? You actually don't see it?
什么
What?
亲爱的  你在跟罗斯约会
Honey, you're dating Ross.
不  菲比  我在跟洛斯约会
No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
洛斯就是罗斯  洛斯  罗斯
Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
史提  史里
Steve, sleeve.
好  没有人叫那种名字
OK. No one is named sleeve.
菲比  你到底在鬼扯什么
Phoebe, what the hell are you talking about?
除了名字相似之外  对不起  我看不到你看到的
Other than their names being similar, I'm sorry,I do not see what you're seeing.
告诉你
For your information...
是赌"胜"  不是赌"圣"
...it's a card sharp, not a card shark.
你错得太离谱了
You could not be more wrong.
你可以试  可是你不会成功
You could try, but you would not be successful.
我先倒杯咖啡  再回来看你们互戳眼睛
I'm gonna get some more coffee before the pinching and eye-poking begins.
我知道你的问题出在哪里
I know what your problem is.
是吗
Oh, you do, do you?
你嫉妒
You're jealous.
嫉妒什么
Of what?
你嫉妒我是个真正的医生
You're jealous because I'm a real doctor.
你是牙周病的医生
Hey, you're a doctor of gums.
那是人能够研究的最小的人体器官
That's the smallest body part you can major in.
就像是第一天才教你用牙线  第二天就发你文凭了
Looks like, Day one, floss. Day two, here's your diploma.
你给我听着
You listen here
-不  让我说完  -不  你让我说完
- No. Let me finish. - No, let me finish.
不  你让我说完
No, you let me fin...
乔伊走时有没有说他打算怎么做
Did Joey say what he was gonna go when he left?
没有  我想他自己也不知道
No. I don't even think he knew.
你会为一份好工作跟别人上床吗
Would you sleep with somebody to get a great job?
不知道  我得跟谁上床
I don't know. Who would I have to sleep with?
我
Me.
我为什么得跟你上床
Why would I have to sleep with you?
这是我定的  这工作你到底要不要
It's my game. You want the job or not?
早
Morning.
你去哪里
Where you going?
我要跟鲍比去小木屋度周末  记得吗
Bobby and I are going away for the weekend. Remember?
带那么多酒干什么
What's with all the bottles of liquor?
怎么了  鲍比又开始喝酒了
What's going on? Is Bobby drinking again?
不  这不是给他的  是我自己留着喝的
Oh no no, this is not for him, this is for me.
这样他会很清醒
That way he's still sober
而我会觉得他的鞋带笑话好笑多了
but I find his stories about shoelaces much more amusing.
天啊  他连敲门都这么乏味
God! Even his knock is boring!
-我马上就好了  -我可以跟你谈一谈吗
- I'll be ready in a second. - Uh, can I talk to you a minute?
可以
Sure.
我真的很难开口
This is really hard for me to say.
天啊  你又开始喝酒了
God. You fell off the wagon!
不是
Oh, no, no.
是关于你的
It's about you.
我怎么了
What about me?
我想你或许有酗酒问题
I think you may have a drinking problem.
你是说这些
What, these?
不  这些事擦伤口用的
No, these are for cuts and scrapes.
我现在无法投入一段相互依赖的关系当中
Look, I'm not strong enough to be in a codependent relationship right now, OK?
该死
Oh, shoot.
-不管怎么样  我希望我们还是朋友  -好
- Well, anyway, I hope we can be friends. - OK.
保重了
Take care.
-你也是  -再见
- You too. - Goodbye.
怎么了
What happened?
我们分手了
We kind of broke up.
这些酒谁要
Does anybody want these?
我拿一瓶
I'll take one.
我有时拿着这种东西  假装我是个巨人
Sometimes I hold stuff like this and pretend I'm a giant.
复试结果怎么样
How'd the callback go?
简直不可思议  我一进去  她就对我大展手脚
It was unbelievable. I walked in there and she was all over me.
-结果呢  -我就是办不到
- What did you do? - I couldn't do it.
我告诉她我不想那样得到角色
I told her I didn't want the part that way.
干得好
Good for you!
等等  我离开她办公室之后
But wait, wait, wait! Then after I left her office...
她追我到电梯  给了我一个更重要的角色
she caught up with me at the elevator and offered me a bigger part.
所以呢
So, and?
所以  各位面前站的是
So, you are now looking at
神经外科医生  德雷克·拉莫雷
Dr. Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon...
至少会在四集里面出镜
... recurring in at least four episodes!
好了  我去洗澡了
All right, I gotta go shower.
你们听说我被瑞秋甩了吧
I guess you guys heard Rachel dumped me.
是的  很遗撼  兄弟
Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
她说我会让她想起另外一个人
She said I remind her too much of somebody.
你们知道那个人是谁吗
Any idea who she's talking about?
我知道  是鲍勃·萨吉特
Oh, I do. It's Bob Saget.
她讨厌他
She hates him.
朱莉
Hey, Julie!
最近好吗
How are you doing?
我不知道  没有了罗斯  的确很不对劲
I don't know. I mean, it's definitely weird not being with Ross,
但我还好吧
... but I guess I'm doing okay.
事实上  我带了一些他的东西...
Actually, I've got some of his stuff that he....